jagobd.com 2016-05-07

# Privacy Policy - JagoBD

**Privacy Policy:**

Jagobd.com has concern that you care about how your personal information is used and shared and we take care your personal information very strongly.  Users must agree with our privacy policy as following below.

 **Personal identification information:**

Jagobd.com does not collect user personal identification information automatically. User personal information like name, email address and message is collected only when user voluntarily submit through our contact form. We may reply to user via email in return of their messages. However, we collect this information to enhance user experience.

 **Non-personal identification information:**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, IP address, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site.

 **How we protect your information:**

Our Site is in observance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users. We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others.

 **Minors:**

If you are under 18 years old, you may not use the Services or provide any of your personal information including, but not limited to, your name, address and email address.

 **Miscellaneous:**

This Privacy Policy constitutes the entire agreement between you and us with respect to the privacy policy related to the Services. No changes to the Privacy Policy shall be made except by a revised posting on this page by us.

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of England applicable therein, without regard to conflict of laws. You irrevocably consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in England in the City of London in connection with any action arising out of or related to this Privacy Statement or their subject matter. You waive any objection based on lack of personal jurisdiction, place of residence, improper venue or forum non-convenience in any such action.

If any court having competent jurisdiction holds any provision of this Privacy Statement invalid or unenforceable in any respect, such provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permitted by law, and the remaining provisions of this Privacy Statement shall continue in full force and effect. No waiver of any provision of this Privacy Statement shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such provision or any other provision of this Privacy Statement.

You have the right to access your information held by Jagobd and, where necessary, to have it amended. You can also request not to receive marketing information from Jagobd.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons:**

Like many companies, we use “cookie” and/or “web beacon” technology. Cookies may tell us whether you have accessed the Services before and what material you have viewed. Web Beacons are tags that can monitor the behavior of a user accessing the Services.

Each time a user accesses the Services, we store a temporary ‘cookie’ in the browser files of that subscriber’s computer or mobile device. This cookie is used during your connection with the Services to allow you free access to the Services, and to use the Services without repeatedly requiring you to re-enter your user name and password. When you log off or leave the Services, the cookies file is automatically removed.

The cookies do not provide us with any way to contact you.

You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set — each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences — however, you may have to enable cookies from in order to use and access some of the Services.

Information recorded through web beacons is used to report anonymous individual and/or aggregate information about our users.

By using the website you accept the use of cookies in relation to your use of the Services.

 **Third-Party Links / Google Adsense:**

Ads appear on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve advertisements to Users based on their visit to our Site. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, location etc. You may know about the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

 **Changes in Privacy Policy:**

This privacy policy is updated on 30 July 2014.  We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revised terms. It is your responsibility to check periodically for any changes we may make to the Privacy Policy and your continuing to access the Services indicates your acceptance of any current Privacy Policy. If you have any question about our privacy policy please contact from this page [Contact Us ].

 **How to Contact us:**

By e-mail to: [info@Jagobd.com](mailto:info@Jagobd.com)

By Post/Address:

Bangladesh: Jagobd IT Solution’s Road#5, Block#C Banasree, Rampura, Dhaka-1219

UAE: Hamdan St. Yousuf Center, Abu Dhabi UAE.

Italy: Piazza Di Porta San vitale, 4 Bologna, Itlay.

Registered in Bangladesh, Company Number 03-028388

Last updated 30 July 2014
